A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accessions 44847, 45144, 45238, 45268, 51901 51962), 1972-2010., Extent: 37 cu. ft. (37 boxes).
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Planning and Research Division: Senior Home Equity Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Suffolk RHA (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 6)
  - Planning and Research Division: Suffolk RHA (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Research Division: Suffolk RHA - Newspaper articles (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Programs and production (Acc. 45238), 1972-1979 (Box 2)
  - Programs and production (Acc. 45238), 1974-1978 (Box 2)
  - Programs and production - Current programs and history of production (Acc. 45238), 1972-1980 (Box 2)
  - Public Safety, Secreaty of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - REACH Program (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - REACH Program (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - REACH Program (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - REACH Program (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Real Estate Advisory Board (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 4)
  - Real Estate Advisory Board (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Residential Indoor Plumbing Program (Acc. 44847), 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Residential Indoor Plumbing Program (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 6)
  - Resource Planning Team meeting (Acc. 51901), 2009 (Box 1)
  - RFP responses on financial study (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 2)
  - Rural Economic Development Information and Miscellaneous Reports (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - SD Leadership Team (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-Mar (Box 2)
  - SD Leadership Team (Acc. 51901), 2009 Apr-June (Box 2)
  - SD Leadership Team (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Sept (Box 2)
  - SD Leadership Team (Acc. 51901), 2009 Oct-Dec (Box 2)
  - SED Quality Performance Awards (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 7)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Multifamily (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Multifamily (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Multifamily (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Multifamily (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Single family (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Single family (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Single family (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: Single family (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: SP/HCUP (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: SP/HCUP (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: SP/HUD (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance: SP/HUD (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Development (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Development (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Development (Acc. 51962), 2010 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Development (Acc. 51962), 2010 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 July-1992 Fune (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1992 July-December (Box 6)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1993 July-December (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Director's correspondence (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: FHA and Programs (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: FHA Loan Productions Info from HUD (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Golf Tournament (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: HB 774 (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Housing in Jarrett (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Petersburg Disaster Response Task Force (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Resolution Trust Corporation (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Resolution Trust Corporation (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Resolution Trust Corporation (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Rural Home Ownership Opportunity Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Sales Price Limit Adjustment (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Tornado Assistance (Acc. 45268), 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Division: Urban Home Ownership Opportunity Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Southern Growth Policy Board (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Southern Growth Policy Board (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Southern Growth Policy Board (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Southern Growth Policy Board (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: African-American Summit Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Board Retreat (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Board Reunion (Acc. 44847), 1990 Dec (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Brookland Plaza Ceremony (Acc. 44847), 1991 January (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Cary 2000 (Acc. 45238), 2000 April (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Ceremony announcing the 4.5% Program (Acc. 45238), 1992 April (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Channel 57 Broadcast on Housing Options for Older Adults (Acc. 44847), 1991 March (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: CHAS Staunton (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Chesapeake Crossing Groundbreaking (Acc. 44847), 1991 Decmeber (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: CLE Seminar on Construction Law and Public Contracts (Acc. 45268), 1994 November (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Bateman's Housing Conference (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Olin's Housing Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 October (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Payne's Housing Conference (Acc. 45238), 1993 Feb (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Pickett's Housing Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 April (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Scott's Housing Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 April (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Sisisky's Housing Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 November (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Congressman Sisisky's Housing Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 June (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Damascus Opening (Acc. 44847), 1990 Apr (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Danville Affordable Housing Program (Acc. 44847), 1991 August (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Delegate Robinson's Constituent Forum (Acc. 44847), 1990 June (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fair Housing Conference (Acc. 45238), 1993 October (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Falls Church City Council (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fannie Mae Meeting in Atlanta (Acc. 44847), 1991 April (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fifth District Housing Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fifth District Housing Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 June (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Focus on the Future Annual Report (Acc. 45144), 1992 June (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fourth District Housing Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: FMHA State meeting (Acc. 45144), 1992 Apr (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Franklin County RHOP Ceremony (Acc. 44847), 1991 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Fredericksburg Realtors grand opening (Acc. 45144), 1992 November (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Harvard Law School Reunion (Acc. 44847), 1990 October (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: HBVA Annual Convention (Acc. 45144), 1992 July (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: HFA meeting with Federal Home Loan Bank (Acc. 45268), 1994 Mar (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Holly Stree Playground Dedication (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Home Builders Association of Virginia Convention (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Home Builders Association of Virginia Convention (Acc. 44847), 1991 April (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: HUD Seminar on Affordable Housing (Acc. 44847), 1991 January (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Human Project Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 Apr (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Interview with Jerry Williams (Acc. 45268), 1994 August (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: IPED Seminar on Tax Credits (Acc. 44847), 1991 October (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Jonesville trip (Acc. 44847), 1990 November (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Leadership Metro Richmond (Acc. 45238), 1993 November (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: LISC Cary 2000 Announcement (Acc. 45268), 1994 September (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Local Initiatives Support Corporation - Richmond Better Housing Coalition Press Announcement (Acc. 44847), 1991 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Lorton Manor Townhomes grand opening (Acc. 44847), 1990 September (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Media Training (Acc. 45268), 1994 August (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Meeting with presidents of minority owned banks (Acc. 45144), 1992 June (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Meeting with Robin Miller (Acc. 45268), 1994 September (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Miscellaneous (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: N-PAC/MAC (Acc. 45268), 1994 August (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Narrow Street Groundbreaking (Acc. 44847), 1990 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: National Association of Realtors Symposium on Real Estate Finance (Acc. 44847), 1990 September (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: National Housing and Rehabilitation Association Spring Forum (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: National Housing and Rehabilitation Association Annual Meeting (Acc. 44847), 1991 March (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: New Clay House Ceremony (Acc. 44847), 1991 June (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Picnic at the Coopers (Acc. 45144), 1992 May (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Pulaski and Lancaster RHOP Ceremonies (Acc. 44847), 1991 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Quarterly staff meeting (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: Roanoke Regional Housing Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 November (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: Scottsville School Opening (Acc. 44847), 1991 April (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Section 8 Existing Program Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 December (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Section 8 Existing Program Update Workshop (Acc. 44847), 1991 June (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Senator Benny Lambert meeting (Acc. 44847), 1991 November (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Senior Housing Management Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Shearson Lehman Hutton Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 Feb (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Staff meeting (Acc. 44847), 1990 July (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Thomas Jefferson HIC Press Conference (Acc. 45268), 1994 Feb (Box 2)
  - Speaking Engagements: VAR Convention (Acc. 45144), 1992 October (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: VEIAA Fall Conference (Acc. 45144), 1991 Oct (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Vern Henley Dinner (Acc. 44847), 1991 September (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia-African Trade Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 November (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: VBA Conference (Acc. 45144), 1992 October (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia Association of Realtors Convention (Acc. 44847), 1990 October (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia Executive Institute Alumni Association Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 May (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia Executive Institute Alumni Association Conference (Acc. 44847), 1991 October (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia Housing Development Authority 20th Anniversary (Acc. 45144), undated (Box 3)
  - Speaking Engagements: Virginia Summit on Drugs (Acc. 44847), 1990 Apr (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: VHDA Staff meeting (Acc. 45238), 1999 Nov (Box 4)
  - Speaking Engagements: VPISU/HIDM Conference (Acc. 44847), 1990 September (Box 5)
  - Speaking Engagements: Welcome to public relations officers (Acc. 45144), 1992 Mar (Box 3)
  - Special Programs: Housing Choice Voucher Program (HCVP)(Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Special Programs: Housing Choice Voucher Program (HCVP)(Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Special Programs: Housing and Urban Development Program (Acc. 51901), 2009 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Special Programs: Housing and Urban Development Program (Acc. 51901), 2009 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Special projects (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Staff attendance at conferences (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 5)
  - State Treasurer (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - TCAP HUD OIG Audit (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 1)
  - Total Quality Managment (Acc. 45268), 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Transportation and Public Safety, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Transportation and Public Safety, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 9)
  - Transportation, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Transportation, Secretary of: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - UHOP (JR's folder) (Acc. 45144), undated (Box 5)
  - United Way Campaign (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 5)
  - United Way Campaign (Acc. 45238), 1992 (Box 4)
  - United Way Campaign (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Urban Home Ownership Program (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 5)
  - VAHCDO: Annual meeting (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - VAHCDO: Correspondence (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - VAHCDO: Workshop (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - VAHCDO, NAHRO, NLHACRA (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 8)
  - VBA Task Force (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - VCDC(Acc. 45144), 1992 January-Apruil (Box 5)
  - VCDC (Acc. 45144), 1992 May-October (Box 4)
  - VHSC - General correspondence (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 7)
  - VHSC - Work session (Acc. 45144), 1991 (Box 7)
  - Veterans Services, Dept. of (Acc. 45238), 1991-1993 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Center for Housing Research (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Center for Housing Research (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Center for Housing Research (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle (Acc. 45144), 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 5)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-December (Box 5)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 3)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle - Research Reports (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle - Research Reports (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Real Estate Circle - Research reports (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1992 November-December (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-February (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1993 March-April (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1993 May-June (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-August (Box 5)
  - Virginia Community Development Corporation (Acc. 45238), 1993 September-October (Box 5)
  - Virginia Executive Institute (Acc. 44847), 1991 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Executive Institue (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Executive Institute (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Housing Coalition (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Coalition (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Coalition (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Housing Commission (Acc. 51962), 2010 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Calendar (Acc. 45268), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Affordable Housing Programs (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Capital (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Disabled (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Elderly (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Employer Assisted Housing (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Federal Programs (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Homeownership (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - NP and Localities (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Poor (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial Information - Rural Housing (Acc. 44847), 1989 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Financial statements (Acc. 44847), 1988 June (Box 2)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority: Golf Tournament (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Foundation (Acc. 45144), 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 44847), 1990 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 44847), 1991 January-June (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 44847), 1991 July-December (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 45144), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 45238), 1993 January-June (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 45238), 1993 July-December (Box 6)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 45268), 1994 January-June (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Fund (Acc. 45268), 1994 July-December (Box 5)
  - Virginia's 2nd African Trade Conference (Acc. 45144), 1991 Nov (Box 3)
  - Weekly Reports (Acc. 44847), 1990-1991 June (Box 7)
  - Watches (VHDA) (Acc. 45238), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Wilma/Warren Fife plates (Acc. 45268), 1994 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 51080), 1972-1997., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Organizational papers, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Commission on State Governmental Management, 1972-1981 (Box 1)
  - Executive Director's correspondence, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1989 Dec 19 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1989 Feb 21 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1989 June 20 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1990 May 15 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1990 Nov 20 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee - Meeting, 1990 Dec 18 (Box 2)
  - Budget Committee, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Building Committee, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Personnel Committee, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Risk Management, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services:Human Resources, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Classification and Pay Study, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: IT, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services:IT Study, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Building Build-out, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Annual Report, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Government Affairs, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Media Inquiries, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Nonprofit Affairs, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: PEP / PIRP, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Communications Division: Staff meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: Indoctrination, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: U.S. Legislators, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat, 1995 Mar (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat, 1994 Nov (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Congressman Boucher's Housing Conference, 1994 May 2 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: RBHC Cary 2000 II Sill Ceremony, 1994 May 10 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: VHDA Golf Tournament, 1994 May 11 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Congressman Payne's Housing Conference, 1994 July 6 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Housing Management Award Lunch, 1994 July 20 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Meeting with CODEL, 1994 Dec (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Meeting with Helen Dunlap re: HUD MF restructuring, 1995 Jan (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Meeting with Alexandria RHA officials, 1995 Aug (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Deputy Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Internal Auditor, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Audit and Managment letters, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Special Projects: Bond Allocation, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Special Projects: Federal Home Loan Bank, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Special Projects: June 1995 Flood - Assistance to Virginians, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Arbitrage Regulations (booklet from Hawkins), 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Finance Division: Evensen-Dodge Study Public Hearing, 1991 Aug 20 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Legal Division, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Multifamily Division: LIHTC Program, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Multifamily Division: Twin Branch Apartments, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Planning and Research Division: Flex Funds, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Planning and Research Division: Preservation of MFLI Housing (LIHPRHA), 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Planning and Research Division: Virginia Housing Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Correspondence, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Agency Head meetings, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Planning meetings with Gov. Allen, 1994 July-Dec (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Agency Head Retreat, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Opportunity Virginia, 1994 Dec 7 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Blue Ribbon Strike Force, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of: Weekly Reports, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 3)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Housing Partnership Fund, 1994 July-1995 Aug (Box 4)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Housing Partnership Fund Administrative Fee, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Housing Partnership Fund Status Report, 1994 (Box 4)